We were both young when I first saw you
(Мы были молоды, когда я впервые увидела тебя)
I close my eyes and the flashback starts, I'm standing there
Я закрываю глаза, и снова вижу, как стою там,
on a balcony of summer air
на балконе летней ночью.
See the lights, see the party the ball gowns
Я вижу огни, вижу бал, вечерние платья...
I see you make your way through the crowd. You say hello
Я вижу, ты идешь сквозь толпу. И говоришь "Привет".
Little did I know
Я и не знала…
that you were Romeo you were throwing pebbles.
Что ты Ромео. Ты бросил камень.
And my daddy said stay away from Juliet
И мой папа сказал "Держись подальше от Джульетты"
And I was crying on the staircase, begging you please don't go, and I said
И я плакала на лестнице, умоляя тебя не уходить, и я сказала...
Romeo take me somewhere we can be alone
Ромео, забери меня туда, где будем только мы,
I'll be waiting all there's left to do is run
Нам остается только сбежать.
You'll be the prince and I'll be the princess
Ты будешь принцем, а я принцессой.
It's a love story baby just say yes
Это история любви, просто скажи "Да"
So I sneak out to the garden to see you
Я вышла в сад чтобы увидеться с тобой,
We keep quite cause we're dead if they know. So close your eyes
Мы очень осторожны, ведь нас убьют, если узнают. Закрой глаза.
Let's keep this down for a little while
Давай ненадолго сбежим из города,
Cause you were Romeo I was a scarlet letter
Потому что ты Ромео, а я была опозорена,
And my daddy said stay away from Juliet
И мой папа сказал "Держись подальше от Джульетты".
But you were everything to me
And I was begging you please don't go and I said
Но ты был всем для меня, и я умоляла тебя "Не уходи", и я сказала...
Romeo take me somewhere we can be alone
Ромео, забери меня туда, где будем только мы,
I'll be waiting all there's left to do is run
Нам остается только сбежать...
You'll be the prince I'll be the princess
Ты будешь принцем, а я принцессой,
It's a love story baby just say yes
Это история любви, просто скажи "Да"...
Romeo save me, they try to tell me how to feel
Ромео, спаси меня, они указывают мне, кого любить...
This love is difficult, but it's real,
Эта любовь трудная, но настоящая,
Don't be afraid
Не бойся.
We'll Make it out of this mess
Вместе мы справимся со всем.
It's a love story baby just say yes, oh,
Это история любви, просто скажи "Да"...
I got tired to waiting
Я устала ждать,
Wondering if you would ever coming around
Гадая, когда же ты придешь...
My faith in you was fading
Моя вера в тебя угасала,
When I met you on the outskirts to town I said
Когда я встретила тебя в пригороде и сказала....
Romeo save me I've been feeling so alone
Ромео, спаси меня, я так одинока
I keep waiting for you but you never come
Я ждала тебя, но ты не приходил
Is this in my head, I don't know what to think.
Это только в моей голове? Я и не знаю что думать.
He kneels on the ground and pulled out a ring and said
Он встал на колено, вытащил кольцо и сказал:
Marry me Juliet you'll never have to be alone
Выходи за меня Джульетта, и ты никогда не будешь одна...
I love you and that's all the reason for
Я люблю тебя и знаю это точно,
I talk to your dad, go pick out a white dress
Я говорил с твоим папой, можешь выбирать белое платье,
It's a love story baby just say yes
Это история любви, просто скажи "Да"
Cause we were both young when I first saw you
Мы были молоды, когда я впервые увидела тебя....